## Connor Meth

Hoboken, NJ, 07030 | 908-698-1404 | connormeth27@gmail.com

Github: ccmeth27 | Portfolio

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming with a background in Software Quality Assurance. Possess strong problem solving and time management skills that provide a company with an efficient and reliable asset. As a former college athlete and senior captain, I gained the knowledge of how to work within a team and also how to lead.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, React.js, React Native, Redux, SQL, CSS, HTML.

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

## Cinebinge - Git Frontend | Git Backend | Demo

Movie and TV streaming availability app with Tinder-esque swipe functionality

- Utilized React Navigation to build a Stack Navigator for authorization and a Bottom Tab Navigator to switch between main screens
- Built the Swipe feature using the React Native Deck Swiper package
- Designed modals that open when tapped which provide more detailed information on the specified movie/show
- Used JSON Web Tokens and localStorage to store encrypted user information client-side.
- Obtained relevant Movie/TV data from Guidebox and OMdb APIs

### Sports Marquee - Github | Demo

A virtual "Stock Ticker" for sports enthusiasts. Displays pre-game betting odds, live scores, and fantasy sports statistics for multiple sports.

- Developed an infinitely scrolling feed of up-to-date sports data with React.js
- Styled using custom HTML and CSS to replicate a physical stock ticker

# Hungry Hungry Jeffs - Github | Demo

JavaScript/HTML game based on Hungry Hungry Hippos featuring my classmate Jeff alongside famous people named Jeff.

- Pair-programming project.
- Designed most of the front-end styling
- Built an image carousel showcasing the different Jeffs in the game
- Implemented background music to replicate a retro arcade game

### **EXPERIENCE**

Quality Assurance Analyst, Arteric, Summit, NJ

10/2018 - 04/2019

- Primary QA resource for the complete redesign of a global oral care company's e-commerce website
- Maintained and executed test plans for multiple global pharmaceutical companies

Quality Assurance Analyst, SportsRecruits, Brooklyn, NY

12/2017 - 08/2018

- Point person between the Software Development team and the customer facing teams
- Manually tested major new feature releases on all major browsers and operating systems
- Prioritized inbound bug reports and maintained a backlog with issues to be solved in upcoming sprints

### **EDUCATION**

Flatiron School 09/2019 - 01/2020

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

**Quinnipiac University**, Hamden, CT Bachelor of Science, Marketing

08/2012 - 05/2016